There was a funeral. Oh, I see.
Okay, well, we're live now.
I was talking about something dangerous.
Dangerous.
I was just saying...
Don't hit people with snakes!
It's disrespectful to snakes!
I'm not ignorant.
Wow, it's been a really bad day.
But I guess if you get hit with something like that all the time, you develop a tolerance.
Right?
I'm sure it would.
Oh, but...
It's not moving.
I'm getting used to it.
Let's get a real one in there sometime.
No, no, no, no, it's so bad
Oh, it's too tight, it's too tight when it moves
I don't want to change.
How many times are they going to work today?
They're getting used to it.
You all know what I'm talking about.
Collect them again. I can't tell you how many times I've done that this week.
I've been playing with bugs all week. That's right.
It really is, isn't it?
So, hello, everyone. Good evening.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
As most of you have guessed.
This week, Kokun just turned 17.
Kokon...
What's the matter? Are you worried about something?
No, no, no, no, no, no...
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Well then, let's get on with the program.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please, please, please, please, please, please!
I'm sure you got it.
So, how's it going?
Well, well, well...
Anyway... this week... in particular... we've received many letters from you.
I'm so happy. I'm sure many things happened.
I see.
That's right. I heard you went to Kokon's birthday party.
Yes.
I went to the launch of the photo book...
Anyway, everyone was amazing.
So, let's go!
Let's go!
Let's go play!
Don't go.
It's work.
Okay, so, first of all...
Uh... uh, I like this one.
Let's see...
Oh, there's already so many that have already gone up!
Wow!
What should we do?
First of all, the Gundam is in Yokohama right now.
A life-size one.
It's going to run out in March.
Yes, yes, yes.
The Gundam that watched over Yokohama for so long...
Yes, yes...
So, for the last time, there are probably many of you who went to see it last month...
I'm so glad to hear that!
Well, first of all, let me introduce you to our special envoy, the cat-tongue urchin, from Isogo Ward, Yokohama City, who has been watching over the city of Yokohama for the past month.
Admiral Master.
Yes, sir.
Karimun Riah Sawapon.
The lovely Ebichu no Bite-chan, Comba Devil.
Comba Devil
One Drop Master in Gundam Factory
Master
Yes, sir.
It ends at the end of March.
Yes.
Well, you see, the Gundam moves like this.
That's right...
That big thing...
Yes.
It's amazing.
Send me a picture of it, like this.
Wow!
This is Yokohama.
Amazing!
Wow!
This is amazing, isn't it?
It's the first Gundam, isn't it?
Wow.
Well, for those who went...
I heard that many people cried.
That's the story.
Is that true?
Yes.
At the end...
I wish I could have seen it.
Yes, it would have been nice.
By the way...
That's why...
I've been into Gundam lately.
That's right.
The master finally told me.
A little late, isn't it?
A little late.
I think it started with you, rather than me.
That's right.
When Mayama-san came.
Yes.
I was hit by that gun-harassment.
A double blow.
Double
Double Ganharas.
Double Zeta Gundam
I had a Gundam, so...
That's right.
I've been watching it ever since.
How does it feel?
How do you feel?
I wonder.
What do you mean?
I don't know.
It's like a breakup show.
No, no, no.
Well, yeah, maybe.
But that's the closest I can get.
Heh.
Anyway, yeah, I could see that in Yokohama all the time.
Yeah.
It was amazing.
For how long?
How long has it been?
Is it long?
Three years, maybe four.
It's been about four years, right?
Because I...
You said you wanted me.
I did.
On location.
You said that?
I had just arrived.
Oh, really?
I've been saying it.
So you've already said it.
Finally.
I don't know what else to say, Mr. Devigo.
Mr. Yamato.
Thank you very much.
The first one says December 2020.
So that's 4 years.
Four years.
I said goodbye to the Gundam that had been protecting Yokohama since
I feel like crying
I wish I could stay in Yokohama forever
Should I call it like Amuro?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like crying
I wish I could stay in Yokohama forever, Mr. Bright.
Gundam, you were looking at this view.
Wait a minute... that's great.
Thank you.
You have a faraway look in your eyes.
Gundam!
This... this... that...
What?
What's it called?
You can see it from above?
Oh, really?
It's this high up.
Wow!
This is nice.
This is the Marine Tower.
I've always wanted to go there.
I think there's a TV station around here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it's around here.
Yes, it is.
Around here.
This is...
Master, is this view okay?
It's not.
Oh, no.
It's impossible.
Even through the Gundam?
Impossible, impossible, impossible!
It's not about the Gundam or anything.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter.
It's got nothing to do with space wars.
But if it's a bungee jump where you can see every inch of the Gundam...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Ultimate Quest.
It's hell, in more ways than one.
But if you jump, you can see every part of the Gundam at close range while you're falling.
It's not that easy!
Before that, I don't understand why you plan to bungee jump to see the parts at close range.
Well, you know...
Even if you don't jump, you can still see them, right?
I don't care if they hang you up like this.
It's like an event where you can bungee jump and see what you want to see.
But there is a possibility of collision.
Scary, scary, scary...
Well, well, well... let me think about it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, there's one more thing...
I like this one, too... for a change.
Yes...
Mr. Sagamihara
Thank you very much.
He often sends me pictures of his motorcycle tours.
Motorcycle riders tend to be attracted to the edges... of Japan's main island, Honshu... the westernmost point of Japan... this is Kanzaki-hana...
I think it's in Nagasaki.
I think this is Nagasaki Prefecture.
I think it's in Nagasaki Prefecture.
I've been there.
This is the flower I mentioned earlier.
It's called "Nihon Hana" (Japanese flower).
It's a rose.
The real tip.
I see...
I see.
Let's see...
It looks like this.
Oh, wow.
There's something up there.
There's a monument to the westernmost point.
Wow, that's nice.
The westernmost point of Honshu.
It's a bright blue
I like this technique Devil.
I've had it done so far
It's dangerous. It's really dangerous.
It's dangerous
Yes, yes, yes, yes
And...
And also...
I like this one too.
Canek GC Factory
Yes, thank you.
The other day, right?
The master
when he got a part-time job.
Anyway, he's really strong when it comes to beauty.
When it comes to beauty, he's really overwhelming.
heh heh heh heh heh heh heh
But when it comes to beauty
When it comes to beauty, he suddenly says
What are you doing?
Your complexion.
It's like he's apologizing to himself.
That's the kind of air you give off.
And at that time...
I don't know...
Like, if someone who hasn't done it before does it, it'll be really beautiful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm not doing anything.
If I did it like this, would it be so beautiful?
I said, "If I do it like this, will it be really beautiful?
At that time, Sarpong said
I said, "What?
Maybe it's like a beautiful Gian...
And he replied, "Yes, like a beautiful Gian.
That was brilliant. I laughed so hard.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I'll send it to you.
Oh!
You're a beautiful master.
They dunked me in the lake once.
Come back to the surface.
You and your beautiful master.
Heh heh heh.
I got all busted up at once.
It's true.
Your hair is so soft.
It's so white!
Your cuticles are so shiny!
I'm in a bit of trouble.
No, it's funny.
Yes, it is.
And you know what?
This is exactly how it's supposed to go.
You know what?
You know...
Mariko became a blonde.
And...
It's been a while since I've worked here.
I thought...
You know...
She changed her image so drastically.
I said, "Why don't you change the name a little too?
So we changed our name to Mariko the Gold.
I see.
That's a long time.
Is that...
Well...
We talked about it a lot.
But surprisingly, it didn't feel strange at all.
I see.
Mariko has a pretty flamboyant face to begin with.
I don't think she'd look so good with blonde hair.
It looked really good on you.
Not at all.
But...
It's time for me to get my hair done.
Bububububub bleach?
Bleach.
I'm thinking of doing it.
Bleach?
Bleach.
I told her what color I wanted.
Mariko said, "Blonde hair.
But if I had blonde hair, we'd both be blondes.
I'd be Master the Gold too.
I was talking about how hard it would be.
When she heard that...
Atsunee drew a picture for me.
Thank you very much.
He said, "This is it.
This is it.
You know... really...
If Riko turns blue...
You'd be Gru?
Mariko the Blue.
But when she finally loses her color...
I'll become Super Mariko.
Can I join the Super Mariko Brothers?
I'm afraid I'll get in trouble.
Dangerous?
Yes, it's dangerous.
Master the Gold like this.
This is so cool!
This is...
It looks like it could be a statue of something.
Looks crazy strong.
It's going to sell for a lot.
I'm trying to sell it.
If we lock him up, we can sell it for a lot.
Sure, sure.
I like it. It's cool.
That's why I'm here.
And... you know Coc N' Coc?
Does he like curry?
Yes, he does.
Then I'll give you this.
I'll do it.
No, I won't.
A little.
Well, well, well.
But so-so.
By the way, there is a unique curry in the region, just like ramen noodles.
There is a bus center in Niigata Prefecture, near Niigata Station, like Basta in Shinjuku,
People waiting for buses often have a lot of time on their hands, especially highway buses.
There is a so-called "stand-up noodle store" that serves curry,
It became so popular by word of mouth that it is now a Niigata specialty.
I heard that.
I've been there before.
Have you been here before? It's called "Bus Center Curry.
First of all, the night commuter pirates in Suginami Ward, Tokyo, went there exactly.
This is what it looks like.
There's a huge line.
Lots of people lined up, of course.
It's very popular.
Is this a nationwide event?
Nationwide.
It's a national event.
It's a nationwide event.
It's a nationwide phenomenon.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I like it.
The curry is also very famous, but anyway, it's makkihiro.
It looks delicious.
It looks like this.
You can't see the rice.
You can't even see it.
It looks like a curry made by a mother.
I thought it would be sweet, but in fact, it has a sour taste.
It's authentic.
It's very authentic.
It's nice.
It's amazing.
What he is trying to say this time is that when you eat here, you eat it with a spoon.
The spoon has an imprint of the bus center on it.
That's right.
On the spoon. I told them to take a look at it.
I heard that you can eat with a spoon like this.
I love it. It's so cute.
For someone who likes it, it makes me very happy.
Because, you know...
Maybe, you know.
Maybe they will go home, but when they get there, they will say, "Oh, here they are.
That's true.
Yes, yes. Retort pouches are available these days.
That's right.
It's so famous.
No, it's good.
Yes, it's good. Yes, yes, yes. Well, well, well, well.
If you have any more letters, please send them to us.
So, here it is....
Well, well, well...it's your birthday, isn't it?
Please, let me ask you one question about the play.
I'd like to ask you a question about your playing.
You gave me a ukulele once, didn't you?
The ukulele is at home.
Well, it's in the house, so it's in the house, but a ukulele is not something you put on display.
It's not for display.
I'll probably have to play it at Deville's someday.
I'm so upset. It's like an obligation.
I don't know...
Maybe Kaho's doing it, too.
I'm sure I'll get a chance to do it.
No, if you're thinking about it, do it.
By all means... by all means... not at all.
I was a little worried.
I've got it at home.
I've prepared something for you again. Thank you very much.
What is it this time?
A violin or something?
A series of musical instruments?
I can't do it. I can't do it.
But the staff told me to keep an eye out for it.
Yes, it's something...
It's amazing!
It's huge!
It's amazing.
Big... like this.
Look at that.
It's a beautiful bag, and...
What's a "kororo"?
Kororo.
Gummi.
Could it be...
Possibly.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
We also have a Devil's Charge!
Devil's Charge is here to wish you a happy birthday, Mr. Devil's Touch.
Thank you very much.
Other than that...
Mr. Kashihige
Mr. Kahiho...
Mr. Kahiho
Mr. Shiranui Kaikai
We have received
Yes, I have.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. There's a lot here.
What's the first one? Space gummies.
I've been curious about these. They're space gummies.
I've never seen them here before.
It's a cute package.
Wow, it really looks like a space suit.
And these too.
Ginza Senbiya's bite-sized fruit jelly.
Jelly? Jelly?
Gummi! Thank you!
Wow, it's in a super cute box!
Yes, a can.
A can.
Wow, it's huge! Don't tell me it's gummy too!
What? Wow! They have gummi bars this big?
Momosuki and Shiki are wishing you good luck with your new country.
Thank you, Mr. Jelly.
Rustle, rustle, rustle, rustle...
That's a lot of rustling.
He's using his tongue to sparkle.
Wow, wow, wow.
Amazing! Nagano Purple, Sky Willie, Shine Muscat, Sato Nishiki, Tamura Mikan, Lafrance...
Sato Nishiki, Tamura Mikan and LaFrance.
All over Japan. Sue-Gooey!
So cute!
I've never seen this before. Is "Cororo" a famous gummy maker?
That's the famous one.
Wow, that's great! Thank you!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I'm all about gummy bears.
So many gummies!
I mean, this is perfect.
Ms. Hirai, Mr. Nagaoka is also Devil Charged.
Thank you very much.
Happy birthday to our country.
One by one, one by one, on the air.
Wow!
This is bad.
May I see them?
These are all famous fruits from all over Japan.
Yes, like Nagano purple.
Wow!
You already opened it.
So you're interested in space gummies.
There's a lot of them.
Are you sure? Thank you.
I see... each one is like this.
Like this.
Wow, they're beautiful.
What do you see? The universe.
I see it.
Did you see it?
Yum! Yum!
I'll have some.
It tastes like grapes and lactobacillus!
It's really good!
It tastes a little like yogurt.
This is good!
It is delicious!
Thank you very much.
Who are you talking to?
Thank you.
Oh, no.
I've never seen coloros in a box like this.
It's such a big box.
They don't look like gummy bears, do they?
Yes, they do.
Bacto-min.
Mr. Yoon Hee of Zadar, too.
Mr. Yoonhee of Zadar said, "Kokum, good luck with your dream!
Toward your dreams.
Nice words.
Devil's Charge, sir.
Thank you very much.
But this...
It's different from the usual broadcasts.
It's got a different texture.
What's this?
Amazing.
It tastes like cola.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh.
I won't have to worry about gummy bears for a while.
That's true.
But I'd eat them right away.
He's going to eat it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well.
So, let's see...
From Kokun.
For those of you watching the live broadcast.
I got a lot of Devil's Charge.
Thank you very much.
Oh, you mean like that?
I'm 17 years old, so...
I've said a lot of things about my aspirations.
I have a lot of people closest to me right now.
My near-term goal right now is to be in a magazine called ZIPPER.
I'm going to participate in a magazine called ZIPPER
ZIPPER magazine's general election for idols.
I'm still participating in it.
And if I come in first
I'll be able to do a solo project in the summer issue.
That's amazing!
What's that?
That's exciting!
Come on, it's exciting!
That's empty.
And you're number one.
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
I'm sure we'll be able to spread the word
I'm sure we'll be able to spread the word about the museum level.
I hope you all can help me.
What should I do?
What we can do now
Please buy a copy of ZIPPER's Shungo
and fill out the paper survey in the ZIPPER
and a web-based survey.
1 point for the web survey
and 10 points for the paper survey.
Then, please fill out both of them
Write a lot, write a lot, write a lot.
Write
I'll write a lot.
I'd like to ask you to do that.
I see.
Let's go home and buy some more.
ZIPPER.
It's on sale March 29th.
March 20?
March 29th.
I'm sure you'll be able to find it in stores.
So it will be available in stores in a little while.
The day after tomorrow.
That makes me nervous.
I'm not in the mood.
But if we win first place or something, then all kinds of things will happen.
I'm sure Yuno's work will expand in the future.
Oh, wow.
This is really unifying, isn't it?
I want to be a professional baseball player! In the summer!
Well, well, well, well, well... so I guess we're almost done with the live broadcast... so let's get to it.
I'll see you all next week at 8:00 p.m.
See you next week at 8:00 a.m. and 8:00 p.m.
Amazing!